JAY BHANUSHALI

UI DEVELOPER



+91 9408555682



jaybhanushali78692@gmail.com



vijapur(382870), Gujarat, India



https://www.linkedin.com/in/jay-bhanushali04



https://jaybhanushali4.github.io/portfolio/

I am a UI developer who is creating visually appealing and user-friendly interfaces for applications and software. I use my expertise in front-end development, HTML, CSS, and JavaScript to translate design concepts into functional and interactive user interfaces.

EXPERIENCE

UI DEVELOPER

BISAG-N

May 2023 - Present

- Implement front-end development using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.
- Continuously improve skills and stay updated with emerging design trends.

WEB DESIGNER

Yudiz Solutions Limited

Jan 2022 - Apr 2023

- Create visually appealing and user-friendly websites.
- Ensure responsive and mobile-friendly designs.
- Collaborate with web developers for seamless implementation.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING

SPCE

2018 - 2022 (8.4 CGPA)

HSC

Ash Secondary School 2016 - 2018 (64%)

SSC

The Forward High School 2015 - 2016 (77%)

EXPERTISE

- HTML
- CSS3
- Bootstrap
- JavaScript

- jQuery
- Wordpress (Template)
- React JS (Basic)
- Front End Coding

- · Problem-Solving
- Design Thinking
- Web Design
- Creative & Professional

PROJECTS

Real Estate:- http://webprojects.cloud/html/real-estate/home.html

Land NFT :- http://webprojects.cloud/html/land-nft/

Market Squawk :- https://themarketsquawk.com/

Food Motion :- https://www.foodmotionnetwork.com/

Objktize :- https://www.objktize.com/

Dangee Dums :- https://www.dangeedums.com/

Technologies

HTML

CSS

Bootstrap

jQuery

JavaScript